Finding Aid for James J. Duderstadt Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- Digital Documents
  - University of Michigan Presidency, 1986-1997; 5397 original digital files (393 MB)
    - Speeches, 1986-1996; 821 original digital files
      - 1988-1989 Speeches, 124 files
        - Commencement-Fall-1988, 12/17/1988
        - UMF Commencement, 12/20/1988
        - Rose Bowl-1989, 12/27/1988
        - Alumni Talks--Summer 1989
        - Detroit Economics Club 1.1, 2/12/1989
        - Football Building Kickoff, 2/17/1989
        - Congressional Breakfast, 2/22/1989
        - Tentative Speech Topics, 2/3/1989
        - Eye on ball, 2016
        - Detroit Economics Club, 2016
        - Develop Leadership, 2016
        - HTS-8_2, 2016
        - Lagatus, 2016
        - Inauguration 1.4, 2016
        - NSFnet Luncheon, 2016
        - NASULGC-San Diego, 2016
        - Regents-Campaign, 2016
        - Senate Republican Caucus, 2016
        - Sue--list, 2016
        - Minority Welcome 2.0, 2016
        - Poem Quotes, 2016
        - 1988-1989 Speeches-Miscellaneous, 2016
        - 3-M Visit, 2016
        - Alumni-March-89, 3/13/1989
        - Pow Wow-89, 3/18/1989
        - Honors Convocation-1989, 3/19/1989
        - Introductions, 3/19/1989
        - Continuity and Chaos, 3/24/1989
        - Case Statement, 3/25/1989
        - Student Recognition Award, 3/26/1989
        - Mortar Board, 3/26/1989
        - Women's Issue, 3/26/1989
        - Basketball Bust -- March 28, 1989, 3/26/1989
        - IPPS Talk, 3/27/1989
        - House Appro Com-3/89, 3/6/1989
        - Coaches Reception, 4/19/1989
        - Rain Commencement, 4/28/1989
        - Commencement-1989, 4/30/1989
        - Phi Beta Kappa, 4/5/1989
        - President's Weekend-5/89, 5/15/1989
        - Internationalization, 5/27/1989
        - Caltech-1989, 5/27/1989
        - Coaches Talk, 5/3/1989
        - International Issues, 5/9/1989
        - Rotary, 5/9/1989
        - Opening, 6/9/1988
        - Big Ten Development Officers, 7/30/1988
        - Blanchard-Tuition, 7/30/1988
        - Diversity Notes, 8/13/1988
        - Futures Talk 1.0, 8/13/1988
        - Deans/EO Kickoff 2.0, 8/14/1988
        - Grad Welcome 2.0, 8/14/1988
        - Parents Orientation 2.0, 8/14/1988
        - New Faculty Welcome 2.1, 8/14/1988
        - State of the University, 8/23/1988
        - Congressional Delegation, 8/24/1988
        - Legislature, 8/24/1988
        - Michigan 2.4, 8/24/1988
        - Student Inaug Address, 8/25/1988
        - Student Inaug Address 1.1, 8/25/1988
        - IFS Reception, 8/30/1988
        - Investments, 9/12/1988
        - State of U-MS, 9/15/1988
        - Inauguration 1.2, 9/16/1988
        - Pres Club, 9/21/1988
        - Prez Fall Weekend 9/23-24, 9/21/1988
        - Congress 1.2, 9/22/1988
        - General Talk, 9/22/1988
        - General Talk-Rose Bowl, 9/22/1988
        - Lead Network 1.1, 9/22/1988
        - Rackham 50th 1.4, 9/23/1988
        - State of U 1.2, 9/23/1988
        - State of U 1.4, 9/23/1988
        - Michigan Mandate 1.4, 9/23/1988
        - Rackham 50th, 9/23/1988
        - UG Ed 1.8, 9/23/1988
        - A List of Talks, 9/27/1988
        - State of U 1.8, 9/30/1988
        - New Faculty Welcome 2.1S, 9/8/1988
        - Freshman Convocation 2.1, 9/9/1988
      - 1989-1990 Speeches, 132 files
        - Pres Council Forum, 1/13/1990
        - MLK Welcome, 1/14/1990
        - MLK Closing, 1/15/1990
        - Science Education 1.4, 1/16/1990
        - P.C.-Forums Speech 1.2, 1/18/1990
        - Center for Visual Arts, 1/21/1990
        - Pres Council Forum-14pt, 1/21/1990
        - EDUCOM Welcome, 10/14/1989
        - JJD Student Letter, 10/15/1989
        - EDUCOM Press, 10/16/1989
        - EDUCOM Panel, 10/16/1989
        - EDUCOM Panel Intro, 10/16/1989
        - State of Univ., 10/2/1989
        - State of University 2.3, 10/2/1989
        - NAE Meeting, 10/21/1989
        - AAU Welcome, 10/22/1989
        - Homecoming-89, 10/28/1989
        - Michigan Mandate, 10/28/1989
        - Education, 11/13/1989
        - Education 1.0, 11/13/1989
        - Education 1.3, 11/13/1989
        - Michigan UM 1.0, 11/19/1989
        - Michigan UM 1.1, 11/19/1989
        - Michigan Add-ins 2.0, 11/23/1989
        - Football Bust 2.0, 11/26/1989
        - RoseBowl (89-90), 11/26/1989
        - Campaign Wrapup, 11/3/1989
        - Aerospace Dedication, 11/3/1989
        - Parents Weekend, 11/3/1989
        - Higher Education 1.0, 11/6/1989
        - Michigan Economy 1.0, 11/6/1989
        - Michigan Higher Ed 1.0, 11/6/1989
        - Michigan Higher Ed 2.2, 11/6/1989
        - Grand Rapids EC, 12/10/1989
        - UGLI Dedication, 12/13/1989
        - American Education, 12/14/1989
        - Commence-Fall-89, 12/14/1989
        - Michigan Add-Ins 1.0, 12/25/1988
        - Education Notes, 12/25/1989
        - RB--Band Rehearsal, 12/26/1989
        - Sac science ed notes, 12/29/1989
        - Press Conference 1.1, 12/9/1989
        - K-12 Education1, 2/10/1990
        - Congressional, 2/27/1990
        - Chemistry Dedication II, 2016
        - Cranbrook Talk, 2016
        - Current Draft, 2016
        - FXB Talk, 2016
        - President's_ MORE 3.0, 2016
        - Teaching vs. Research, 2016
        - PAC-June-90 MORE 3.0, 2016
        - 1989-1990 Speeches-Miscellaneous, 2016
        - Science Education, 2.1, 3/1/1990
        - Appro CommTest1.1, 3/18/1990
        - GM SpiritAwards, 3/23/1990
        - Flint Rotary, 3/25/1990
        - PCForum-Detroit, 3/25/1990
        - Engineering Comm, 4/13/1990
        - Caltech Commencement-89, 4/13/1990
        - Athletes Reception, 4/13/1990
        - Commence-Spring-90, 4/13/1990
        - Student Leadership, 4/13/1990
        - Science Awards, 4/15/1990
        - Overarching Themes, 4/16/1990
        - Bo's Farewells, 4/19/1990
        - Automotive, 4/2/1990
        - Midland Talk, 4/2/1990
        - Rackham, 4/2/1990
        - Addins-1990, 4/6/1990
        - The Economics of..., 4/6/1990
        - United Way, 4/6/1990
        - Basketball Bust-90, 4/9/1990
        - T vs R Notes, 5/12/1990
        - Undergraduate, 5/12/1990
        - President's, 5/13/1990
        - Presidents Club Finale, 5/17/1990
        - Michigan, Mandate 3.0, 5/30/1990
        - Development, 5/31/1990
        - PAC-June-90, 5/31/1990
        - NSF, T&R 1.0, 6/10/1990
        - UG Notes, 6/10/1990
        - Hartford Sermon 2.0(act), 6/27/1990
        - Hartford Sermon 2.1, 6/27/1990
        - Michigan Crossroads 1.0, 6/27/1990
        - Service Awards, 6/5/1990
        - Traverse City Talk, 6/5/1990
        - Manufacturing Forum, 7/11/1990
        - Semiconductor, 7/16/1989
        - Summary 1989-90, 7/19/1990
        - Solar Car, 7/19/1990
        - Michigan Economy 1.0..., 7/2/1990
        - Response, 8/25/1989
        - Freshman Convocation 3.0, 8/30/1989
        - Graduate Welcome 3.0, 8/30/1989
        - Minority Welcome 3.0, 8/30/1989
        - Parents Orientation 3.0, 8/30/1989
        - New Faculty Welcome 3.0, 8/30/1989
        - Newsweek notes, 8/30/1989
        - Major Gifts Address 1.0, 8/31/1989
        - Costs of Education, 8/31/1989
        - Major Gifts Address 2.0, 8/31/1989
        - PresClub-10/89, 8/31/1989
        - Alumni 5.0, 9/11/1989
        - Leadership Network 2.0, 9/11/1989
        - Corporate Remarks, 9/13/1989
        - TalkIdeas--9/89, 9/13/1989
        - Chemistry Lunch, 9/14/1989
        - Intern Forum (9/89), 9/14/1989
        - Old Stuff, 9/14/1989
        - Chemistry Dedication, 9/15/1989
        - Studies in Religion, 9/16/1989
        - Hispanic Heritage, 9/17/1989
        - Michigan Talks 2.0, 9/17/1989
        - Citizens ResCouncil, 9/18/1989
        - LA Dinner, 9/21/1989
        - LA Major Gifts, 9/21/1989
        - Alumni (MajorGifts), 9/26/1989
        - Alumni (Volunteers), 9/26/1989
        - Alumni (Volunteers) 2.0, 9/26/1989
        - Case Statement, 9/26/1989
        - Los Angeles Dinner, 9/26/1989
        - Volunteers Strategy, 9/26/1989
        - State Plan, 9/3/1989
        - NY Business Lunch, 9/30/1989
        - NAACP Talk, 9/8/1989
        - Taubman Conference, 9/8/1989
      - 1990-1991 Speeches, 214 files
        - Doctoral Pipeline Issue, 1/10/1991
        - College Sports 1.1, 1/12/1991
        - College Sports 1.2, 1/12/1991
        - NAE Notes, 1/16/1991
        - MLK Symposium Opening, 1/19/1991
        - UG Notes, 1/19/1991
        - Teaching vs. Research 1.5, 1/20/1991
        - UG Ed 1.8, 1/20/1991
        - Teaching vs. Research 1.3, 1/20/1991
        - UM-WCC Alliance, 1/21/1991
        - Academic Women's, 1/24/1991
        - Investments, 1/27/1991
        - Task Assignment, 1/27/1991
        - President's Advisory Committee on Women's Issues, 1/29/1991
          Restricted until July 01, 2030
        - Reinventing 2.0, 1/8/1991
        - Key Focus Areas, 1/9/1991
        - Michigan Mandate III, 10/13/1990
        - Michigan Crossroads 1.0, 10/14/1990
        - UM Inputs and Outputs, 10/15/1990
        - Maternal and Child Health, 10/18/1990
        - Medical School Discussion, 10/2/1990
        - Dearborn Dedication, 10/25/1990
        - Parents Weekend, 10/26/1990
        - Parents Weekend, 3.0, 10/27/1990
        - Michigan Mandate, 10/28/1990
        - Ethnic Studies Luncheon (10/90), 10/4/1990
        - Santa Fe Institute 1.0, 11/1/1990
        - B) Themes of Future, 11/11/1990
        - C) Demographics, 11/11/1990
        - NASULGC-Activism, 11/14/1990
        - NASULGC-Plan, 11/14/1990
        - Notes, 11/15/1990
        - Resource Issues, 11/15/1990
        - NoCode, 11/18/1990
        - Jjd e-mail, 11/19/1990
        - PC-Safety, 11/19/1990
        - JJD Student Letter, 11/21/1990
        - Michigan Outreach Talk 1.1, 11/22/1990
        - Michigan Outreach Talk 1.0, 11/22/1990
        - Regents-December, 11/22/1990
        - Alumni Talk 6.0, 11/24/1990
        - Visit with science, 11/28/1990
        - Parents Weekend 2.0, 11/3/1989
        - UM Dearborn Comments, 11/5/1990
        - Public Education 4.2, 11/6/1990
        - Engler Addin, 11/9/1990
        - Commence-Fall-90, 12/13/1990
        - Big Ten-UM$, 12/17/1990
        - ITI Meeting, 12/18/1990
        - Big Ten, 12/2/1990
        - Major Gifts Committee 1.0, 12/3/1990
        - Costs, Prices, Values 3.0, 12/6/1990
        - Tanner notes, 12/6/1990
        - To Do-1991, 12/7/1990
        - BHEF Odds and Ends, 2/11/1991
        - Women of Color Awards, 2/21/1991
        - Teaching AND Research 2.1, 2/4/1991
        - Peter Raven, 2/7/1991
        - Armenian Odyssey, 2016
        - Big Ten Admissions_, 2016
        - Black All Campus Alumni_, 2016
        - Campaign_Corporate, 2016
        - Faculty Awards 4.0, 2016
        - Higher Education Offensive, 2016
        - Ideas II, 2016
        - LaMothe Talk 3_20_91, 2016
        - McFee Draft, 2016
        - Library Science 10_90, 2016
        - Nederlander_Lindemer, 2016
        - NSF Forum, 2016
        - Graduate Welcome 3.1, 2016
        - Rackham Opening_, 2016
        - TRIP, 2016
        - Reinventing 1.0, 2016
        - Regents 90-91 Report 3.4, 2016
        - Regents 90-91Report 1.1, 2016
        - Public Education 4.1, 2016
        - UM Tuition_, 2016
        - President's House_, 2016
        - Grad_Gourman_, 2016
        - US_NEWS_1991_Grad_Undergrad_, 2016
        - Regents 90-91 Report 2, 2016
        - 1990-1991 Speeches-Miscellaneous, 2016
        - Mandate Chronology, 2016
        - Spring To-Do, 2016
        - Appro Comm Test 1.1, 3/10/1991
        - Con Bkfst, 3/10/1991
        - Simulator Site Visit, 3/10/1991
        - Brainstorming Ideas, 3/11/1991
        - Campaign Pitches, 3/11/1991
        - Appro Hearings 1.0, 3/23/1991
        - Honors Convocation-1991, 3/23/1991
        - Regents-March, 3/23/1991
        - Appro Hearings, 2.0, 3/25/1991
        - NSF Traineeships, 3/25/1991
        - Press Conference (3/26/91), 3/25/1991
        - Appro Hearings 3.0, (Actual), 3/27/1991
        - Notes for Speeches II, 3/29/1991
        - Campaign/Individual, 3/31/1991
        - UM Press/60th, 3/4/1991
        - Flower Show Opening, 4/10/1991
        - Gerald R. Ford Colloqium, 4/10/1991
        - Michigan Outreach Talk 1.21, 4/11/1991
        - Themes for 1991, 4/13/1991
        - Engler-BRT, 4/17/1991
        - Futures Bibliography, 4/18/1991
        - Top 20 Ranking Undergrad, 4/19/1991
        - PC Notes, 4/24/1991
        - All Graduate Rankings, 4/24/1991
        - Appro Hear PCSUM, 4/27/1991
        - Commencement Notes, 4/27/1991
        - Appro Sum, 4/29/1991
        - Commencement/jjd2, 4/29/1991
        - Governor Arioshi, 4/4/1991
        - Spring Commencement Script, 4/4/1991
        - Steering Committee, 4/4/1991
        - Nursing Centennial (5/2/91), 5/1/1991
        - Attack on Values 1.0, 5/12/1991
        - Attack on Values 1.2, 5/12/1991
        - Summary 1990-91, 5/12/1991
        - Coverletter_Rankings_1.0, 5/13/1991
        - SILS Sympsium (5/13/91), 5/13/1991
        - GormanRankings, 5/14/1991
        - GormanRankings, 5/14/1991
        - PC Notes-HTS, 5/16/1991
        - ICR Points, 5/17/1991
        - Master speech list, 5/17/1991
        - Academic Values 2.2, 5/18/1991
        - AAU PC, 5/19/1991
        - Commencement-JJD Version, 5/2/1991
        - Odds and Ends I, 5/2/1991
        - ICR, 5/21/1991
        - MBRT Dinner, 5/21/1991
        - PC/Mandate Addins, 5/21/1991
        - MBHEF-5/91, 5/22/1991
        - Academic Values 2.3, 5/25/1991
        - Schembechler Hall, 5/28/1991
        - Schembechler Hall Dinner, 5/28/1991
        - 4x6 Template, 5/29/1991
        - Commence-JJD Cards, 5/3/1991
        - Honorary Degree Dinner, 5/3/1991
        - Commence-Cards-JJD-1, 5/3/1991
        - Strategic Marketing Plan, 5/3/1991
        - Strategic Marketing Plan 1.1, 5/3/1991
        - Northwestern Michigan, 5/31/1991
        - Vest Inaugural Lunch, 5/7/1991
        - Academic Freedom 1.2, 5/8/1991
        - Coverletter_Rankings, 5/9/1991
        - Angell Society, Detroit, 6/10/1991
        - Commencement Thankyou, 6/10/1991
        - VPGR, 6/10/1991
        - Ford Testimony, 6/11/1991
        - Appro House Repubs, 6/13/1991
        - Michigan Outreach Talk 1.3, 6/13/1991
        - Ford Oral, 6/16/1991
        - SS Report Card, 6/22/1991
        - MICH MANDATE 3 YR UPDATE, 6/26/1991
        - Sasakawa Foundation, 6/3/1991
        - Futures Notes, 7/1/1991
        - Notes III, 7/1/1991
        - Tanner Meeting, 7/1/1991
        - Regents-June, 7/1/1991
        - RESOURCE, 7/1/1991
        - Student Services Revie, 7/1/1991
        - Regents Annual Report 1.2, 7/16/1991
        - Trip Notes, 7/16/1991
        - Traxler, 7/17/1991
        - AAU Notes, 7/18/1991
        - Regents Budget-91, 7/18/1991
        - Traineeship 1.1, 7/18/1991
        - National Rankings, 7/21/1991
        - Public Concerns, 7/21/1991
        - NSPE Thanks, 7/24/1991
        - SAC Meeting, 7/26/1991
        - Regents Tuition Briefing, 7/5/1991
        - EO Salaries, 8/2/1991
        - Parents Orientation 4.1, 8/22/1990
        - Notes for Speeches, 8/24/1990
        - Physics Notes, 8/24/1990
        - Fresh Convocation 4.3, 8/28/1990
        - Massey, 8/3/1991
        - Freshman Convocation 3.0, 8/30/1989
        - New Faculty Welcome 3.1, 8/30/1989
        - Graduate Welcome 4.1, 8/30/1990
        - Regents-8/90 Report, 8/30/1990
        - Minority Welcome 4.1, 8/31/1990
        - C of C (9/90) 1.2, 9/15/1990
        - Reinventing 1.1, 9/15/1990
        - Senate Assembly 1990 1.3, 9/16/1990
        - Mitsui Dedication, 9/20/1990
        - New Faculty Welcome 3.1, 9/23/1990
        - New Faculty Welcome 3.2, 9/23/1990
        - Faculty Welcome 4.2, 9/24/1990
        - Wallenberg Lecture, 9/25/1990
        - Asian American, 9/28/1990
        - The Age of Knowledge, 9/30/1990
      - 1991-1992 Speeches, 52 files
        - UM Research FIrsts, 1/20/1992
        - Investments, 1/27/1991
        - Progress Talk, 12/1/1991
        - Heisman Dinner (12/18/91), 12/16/1991
        - Campaign Pitch-Alumni, 12/3/1990
        - development Advisory Group, 12/4/1991
        - Peter Raven, 2/7/1991
        - 1992 Add-Ins, 2016
        - Radio Interviews, 2016
        - Minority Data-Play, 2016
        - FY91-92 Salaries, 2016
        - GUIR Report, 2016
        - Trip Ideas 3_26_92, 2016
        - 1991-1992 Speeches-Miscellaneous, 2016
        - Technology Policy 2.4, 2016
        - SOUP-2_92, 2016
        - Woodworth Meeting, 2016
        - Performance Reviews, 2016
        - Technology Policy Text, 3/14/1992
        - Reality Test, 3/24/1992
        - Reality Test 1.0, 3/30/1992
        - Economic Strategy 2.0, 3/6/1992
        - Congressional Breakfast-92, 3/7/1992
        - Themes for 175th, 3/8/1992
        - Cong Bkft 2.0, 3/9/1992
        - Video 3, 4/14/1992
        - Essay Subjects, 4/3/1992
        - Essay-Academic Leadership, 4/3/1992
        - Fiscal video outline, 4/8/1992
        - Odds and Ends I, 5/2/1991
        - Presidential Essays, 5/25/1992
        - ITIC, 5/30/1992
        - Cazzie, 6/3/1992
        - Research Videotape, 6/5/1992
        - Reality Notes 1.0, 7/4/1992
        - Speech Outlines--1991-92, 8/22/1991
        - Fresh Convocation 4.3, 8/28/1990
        - Freshman Parent, 8/28/1991
        - UM Inputs/Outputs, 8/28/1991
        - Freshperson Welcome 5.1, 8/31/1991
        - Parents Orientation 5.1, 8/31/1991
        - Freshperson Welcome 5.2, 9/1/1991
        - Campaign Finale, 9/15/1991
        - Campaign Kickoff, 9/15/1991
        - New Talks, 9/23/1990
        - Presidents' Weekend Finale, 9/24/1991
        - President's Weekend 3.0, 9/25/1991
        - Quotes, 9/30/1990
        - Traineeship 1.4, 9/5/1991
      - 1992-1993 Speeches, 36 files
        - Scientific Integrity 1.2, 1/14/1993
        - Governor's Economic, 1/17/1993
        - Lunch & Learn, 1/26/1993
        - Pres Lec #1, 10/13/1992
        - Alumni Remarks 10.0, 10/14/1992
        - Alumni Remarks 11.0, 10/14/1992
        - Backup of Grosse Pointe Rot., 10/24/1993
        - Faculty Awards, 10/5/1992
        - Football Bust-92, 11/24/1992
        - NSF Commission, 11/6/1992
        - Redraw Boundaries 1.4, 11/8/1992
        - PAC-K-12, 12/2/1992
        - Grand Rapids Rotary, 12/4/1992
        - Rose Bowl-92, 12/7/1992
        - Econ Dinner Group 1.1, 2/12/1993
        - Regents-Fin Aid, 2/18/1993
        - Listen and Learn 1.4, 2/6/1993
        - Listen and Learn 1.6, 2/6/1993
        - Tech Transfer 1.1 (87), 2/8/1993
        - AD Search Notes, 2016
        - Congressional Breakfast, 3/2/1993
        - Science Com Testimony 1.0, 3/2/1993
        - Minority Stu Conf 1.1, 3/2/1993
        - The Year Past, 3/22/1993
        - Alumni Remarks 12.0, 4/13/1993
        - Honorary Degree Dinner, 4/30/1993
        - Commencement Notes, 4/30/1993
        - Grosse Pointe Rotary, 5/11/1993
        - Commencement-JJD Version, 5/2/1991
        - Flint roundtable june 23, 6/18/1993
        - Grosse Pointe Rot. (word), 6/8/1993
        - Fresh Conv-93, 8/28/1993
        - Wallenberg lecture, 9/10/1992
        - Community College 1.0, 9/14/1992
        - Rotary Club - Jan. 24, 9/21/1992
        - Lapeer Rotary 1.1, 9/21/1992
      - 1994-1995 Speeches, 27 files
        - Vision 2010 Talk, 10/14/1994
        - Flint Rotary 1994, 10/18/1995
        - Visitors-11-94, 10/25/1994
        - Anapolis Talk, 10/31/1994
        - Annapolis, 10/31/1994
        - AA Rotary, 11/15/1994
        - Flat Panel Display, 11/15/1994
        - 1994-1995 Speeches-Miscellaneous, 2016
        - OMA Testimony, 3/19/1995
        - Appro Hearings 1.0, 3/2/1995
        - Word Work File D 3, 3/2/1995
        - UM-MSU Statistics, 3/28/1995
        - Parity1.3, 3/9/1995
        - UROP Speech, 4/11/1995
        - Senate Testimony, 4/12/1995
        - State Support Outline, 4/28/1995
        - State Support, 4/28/1995
        - Office of Minority Affairs-Ed S, 4/4/1995
        - Jewish Federation, 4/5/1995
        - High Tech Talk, 4/8/1995
        - Transformation Talk 1.2, 4/9/1994
        - Georgia Tech-Speech, 5/13/1995
        - COMU Retreat 1994, 5/19/1994
        - Op-Ed Cooperation, 5/2/1995
        - Op-Ed UM Service, 5/2/1995
        - Varsity Night, 9/23/1994
        - PAG-1995, 9/27/1995
      - 1995-1996 Speeches, 135 files
        - Women of Color intro, 1/10/1996
        - MSU-Govt-U Research Partnership, 1/19/1996
        - Ann Arbor Rotary, 1/22/1996
        - Ex Com Retreat-1-96, 1/7/1996
        - Chrysler Talk, 10/12/1995
        - UM Future Speech, 10/26/1995
        - Word Work File D 2030, 11/14/1996
        - Free Press Op-Ed, 11/18/1995
        - Football Bust, 12/3/1995
        - Peckham Epilogue, 12/30/1995
        - Change Speech, 12/31/1995
        - Research U Speech, 12/31/1995
        - Michigan's Future 2.0, 12/31/1995
        - Michigan's Future 2.1, 12/31/1995
        - Stump Speech 1.0, 2/12/1996
        - Senate Testimony, 2/14/1996
        - Senate Test Text, 2/14/1996
        - Stump Speech 1.1, 2/20/1996
        - K-12 Talk, 2/25/1996
        - Wiesner Conference, 2/25/1996
        - Wiesner, 2/26/1996
        - Word Work File D 2030, 2016
        - Senate Assembly Slides, 3/14/1996
        - UM-Dearborn, 3/14/1996
        - Affirm Action Op-Ed, 3/18/1996
        - NSB Keynote Talk, 3/18/1996
        - NSB Talk, 3/18/1996
        - Honors Convocation, 3/21/1996
        - UM-Flint, 3/22/1996
        - Public Research, 3/25/1996
        - Public U Data, 3/25/1996
        - Pub U Slides, 3/26/1996
        - Senate Assembly (3-96), 3/3/1996
        - NSB-UC-Davis, 3/30/1996
        - Alumni Talk, 4/10/1996
        - Rackham Commencement 1.0, 4/28/1996
        - Diversity Dinner, 4/28/1996
        - Alumni Dinner, 4/28/1996
        - Commencement-1996, 4/28/1996
        - Operating Manual, 4/6/1996
        - Operating Manual 1.0, 4/7/1996
        - Appropriations-House, 5/1/1996
        - Fund-Raising Themes, 5/14/1996
        - Columbia Symposium, 5/14/1996
        - Digital Librarians, 5/16/1996
        - Medallion Inscription, 5/2/1996
        - Medallion List, 5/2/1996
        - 2-10 Tuition color, 5/20/1996
        - Rackham, 5/20/1996
        - 3-7 aPPublics color, 5/20/1996
        - 2-12 RelatTuition color, 5/20/1996
        - Birmingham, 5/22/1996
        - 6-23 MinPhDDegrees, 5/23/1996
        - 6-25 MinFaculty color, 5/23/1996
        - 6-13 AfAm GradRates, 5/23/1996
        - 5-1 Research $, 5/23/1996
        - 6-26 AfAm Faculty color, 5/23/1996
        - 6-25 MinFaculty, 5/23/1996
        - 6-17 MinUGDegrees, 5/23/1996
        - 6-27 MinSrHires color, 5/23/1996
        - 6-7 AfAm Student%, 5/23/1996
        - 6-23 MinPhDDegrees color, 5/23/1996
        - 6-26 AfAm Faculty, 5/23/1996
        - 6-19 MinMADegrees, 5/23/1996
        - 6-27 MinSrHires, 5/23/1996
        - 6-24 MinGradFellows color, 5/23/1996
        - 6-21 MinProfDegrees, 5/23/1996
        - 6-1 MinStudents, 5/23/1996
        - 6-3 MinStudent %, 5/23/1996
        - 10-10 Approp%All Funds color, 5/24/1996
        - 10-12 ChgMix% color, 5/24/1996
        - 10-15 All Funds color, 5/24/1996
        - 10-17 Approp%OpBud color, 5/24/1996
        - 10-3 Approp/FYES color, 5/24/1996
        - 10-9 Approp&All Fund$ color, 5/24/1996
        - 7-3 WomStudents color, 5/24/1996
        - 7-3 WomStudents, 5/24/1996
        - 7-9 WomFaculty, 5/24/1996
        - 12-2 Private Giving color, 5/28/1996
        - 12-3 Endowed Chairs color, 5/28/1996
        - 2-13 FinAid Comp color, 5/28/1996
        - 13-1 Endowment color, 5/28/1996
        - 2-15 GF FinAid color, 5/28/1996
        - 15-1 Intn Students color, 5/28/1996
        - 16-1 Royalty Revenue color, 5/28/1996
        - 3-9 APPublics color, 5/29/1996
        - 3-10 APPrivates color, 5/29/1996
        - 5-1 Research $ color, 5/29/1996
        - 3-12 ProfPrivate color, 5/29/1996
        - 5-4 Table Research Rank, 5/29/1996
        - 6-17 MinUGDegrees color, 5/30/1996